https://www.themodernfirm.com/privacy-policy/

For ClientsJoin Our TeamSupportRemote
MenuWebsite DesignPortfolioClient WebsitesLogosMarketingOnline Marketing 101Local MarketingSearch OptimizationGoogle Adwords PPCBlogging and WritingAbout UsOur CompanyMeet Our TeamWhy Choose UsTestimonialsBlogQuestion of the WeekCompany NewsGet a Quote – Contact
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to The Modern Firm, LLC (“we”). This privacy policy is intended both to: 1) describe how our website may collect and use information from your Internet enabled device (i.e. your computer, tablet, smartphone or other device — and browsers or apps used to access the Internet), and 2) describe how you may opt out of any such collection and use. Please contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.Data collection and cookies. Features or partners of our website may collect data including, but not limited to: the number of visitors to our site, the time spent on our site and pages clicked, the types of devices used to access our site, and the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors. We use this information to improve our website and marketing. This data is collected by sending cookies (or similar tracking technology) to your device. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; if you previously provided personally identifiable information, however, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties; and this privacy policy does not cover third parties’ use of cookies. You may configure your device to limit or prevent access by cookies, such as to notify you when you receive a cookie, to block all cookies, or to delete existing cookies.Partners and features that collect information. Our website marketing partners or features that collect data as described above may include, among others, Google Analytics, other analytics programs, and Google AdWords remarketing service. Remarketing involves tracking devices that have visited our website in order to display ads for our services on other websites. Use these links to learn how Google uses data it collects, to prevent Google Analytics from using data from your device, or to opt out of Google’s interest-based ads.Information you send us. If you submit your name or contact information to us, we may use it to send you information about our services. You may opt out of receiving further information from us by contacting us or, where applicable, by using an “unsubscribe” option included in our communications. We will not sell or give your personally identifying information to other parties for their own direct advertising purposes.For California residents. As described above, we do not disclose personal information to third parties for their own use in direct marketing. The information above also explains how you may opt out of permitting our website or partners from collecting information from your device.Changes to this policy. We reserve the right to update this policy. If we make updates, we will change the modification date below.Last modified. July 13, 2016
Featured Website Launches
James Bart Leonardi, LLC
http://www.bartleonardi.com/
Richard Lionberger, Attorney
https://www.rll-law.com/View Entire Portfolio
What Our Clients Say
Heidi GoebelGoebel Anderson PCSalt Lake City Utah Litigators
www.gapclaw.com
"Working with the Modern Firm was so easy. Such friendly knowledgeable people. They were prompt and pleasant. They sent reminders without being intrusive. I would definitely recommend them to a colleague.
Read More
"View All Client Reviews
Recent Blog Posts
Dec
1
ADA Accessibility Issues of Websites
December 1st, 2020
Lawyers have many rules to follow. This is something we all learn on just about the first day of law school. Since the internet has become an all but indispensable tool in the practice of law, lawyers have had to apply old rules to a new medium,...
Read More
Nov
16
The Cautionary Side of Working from Home as a Lawyer
November 16th, 2020
Lawyers across the country have had to adapt to several new realities very quickly this year. Because of the COVID-19 pandemic, courts began holding many or most proceedings remotely, and many lawyers had to abandon their offices to work from home....
Read More
Read More From Our Blog
Meet Our Team
Brendan Chard
Kristin Lay, J.D.
Diego Aguirre
Ryan Gough
Bryan Glanz
Michele Johnson
Trinity Reyes
Carmela Orsini, J.D.
Erin Ricchiazzi
Sydney Hellrung
Cullen Webb
Tommy Henry
Laura Slider
Rebecca Fadel King, J.D.
Office Staff
Our ServicesNew Law Firm WebsitesWebsite RescueOnline MarketingProfessional Logo DesignLike What You See? Get In Touch© 2020 The Modern Firm - View Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2020
The Modern Firm
